Music
We're here!
Where are we?
Cosmo World
Yay!
I'm going to get some brochures.
Wait for me.
Okay.
What would you like to ride? What do you guys want to ride?
I don't care what you want.
Anything?
It's fun, I guess.
I've never been.
Yuen doesn't come here often?
No, I've never been.
You don't come often.
I only go once in a while.
I'm surprised.
You seem like a screamer.
I want to ride the Ferris wheel.
No, I don't.
It's stylish.
I just don't think I'm up to it.
Really?
I'm a huge screamer.
You do?
Yeah, I do.
Okay, I get it.
Let's all watch this together.
Okay.
Okay, then.
This way.
What would you like to ride?
The merry-go-round man!
There's so many of them.
All right, let's do something.
Let's go.
Let's just go.
Let's go!
Let's go to Riko.
Let's play basketball!
Kryptonite M will try.
Okay then.
Let's cheer for him.
How many points do you think you can get?
What's this?
It's over 40, right?
Yeah.
It's over 40.
That's enough time, right?
Thirty seconds.
Oh, no.
Here we go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Thirty.
About 30.
What?
Huh?
Oh, my God.
Is it?
Twenty-two points.
It's so hard!
End
The amendment4
I bought a Letcon Star ticket!
I got on. I would like to ride on pink now.
During the ride, I will take pictures from below by car, so we will be divided in a good way.
Shall we understand by men and women?
Oh, I'll guppa with men and women.
Guppa.
Par.
Then, let's go with Anri Suzuki.
Okay, I guess that's good.
Let's go first.
I'll go first.
Okay, see you.
See you later.
Kyushu I.M. and Anri Suzuki are over there.
Yes, probably. Maybe.
I don't know. I can't see them. Not at all.
Oh, there it is.
There's a bald head. There's a bald head.
There it is, there it is.
Is he here? You there?
It was there, it was there, it was there. I saw it for a moment. I think so.
Here it comes, here it comes.
Wow, there it is.
Itchy, itchy, itchy.
Hang in there.
So, as you can probably tell by looking at me now, I've been on this pink ride.
Well, I am tired.
How was it?
I was exhausted at once. It was fun.
It was fun.
Yeah, it was.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I was just joking around.
I was just saying you're back.
I don't know, is that really something to shout about? He said, "Oh, yeah.
I was yelling a lot.
I was a little embarrassed, but that's about it.
Yes.
Next, Isshin and the others will ride on this.
Yes, and the sound of the rhythm, too.
Hey, we can take this just as it comes in, so let's go for the next turn.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm yelling even though there's nothing yet, but there it is. That's it. This is it.
Hey.
This way.
Hey, aren't they coming in a little early?
Are they here?
Oh, here they come.
Is that it? That's not it?
What do you think, guys?
How was it?
Good job, guys. I got it right. Zoomed in.
That sucks. I'm pretty sure my face was done.
How was it? You didn't get wet?
I didn't get wet.
No? You're soaking wet?
Yes, I'm wet.
What? It was all over my face.
Then, since Riichi was filming, what was on Riichi's face came to you.
It was on Riichi.
It was a lot of fun.
It was fun. Please take a picture of us together.
You seem to be having fun.
It was a lot of fun.
But we got some good shots.
It was fun.
The sound of the beautiful voice, you know, that was it.
Well, now that we've taken two shots, let's just have fun.
Let's have fun.
Bye bye.
Let's go.
Wait, it's really nice.
The waterfront, the light...
What waterfront?
It's the water, right here.
A river?
Yes, yes.
It's really nice.
The water.
The light is great.
It's really beautiful.
And the light of the building.
Yeah, it's nice, isn't it?
It's nice, isn't it?
It's really nice.
Can I take a picture for Instagram?
Sure, sure.
I'm taking a picture for Instagram.
For Instagram.
That's what I'm talking about.
This will be in the Insta post.
It's going to be on there.
Please take a look.
It's just a moment like this, isn't it?
You can put memories on the photo.
Don't say it, just remember the memories in your head.
That's right.
The fact that you are taking pictures is already a memory.
That's right. Walking together like this is a memory.
Next, we are going to Fujikyu.
Fujikyu.
All of us.
That's with the nine of us.
Let's go with nine people.
We've lost the arcade, too.
We're going to take a picture of Precura, right?
Hey, let's take a shot of Precura.
Let's take a shot of the Preciura.
What?
Cooking, yogurt, right?
All of it.
Oh, what?
You're pushing it?
Congratulations.
That's great.
Oh, wait.
Most vertical.
Oh, yes.
Here we go.
Wait, I can't see.
I'm sorry.
I can't see you. I can't see you right now.
Wait, I'm sorry.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
How's it going?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's over.
Gross, huh?
I fixed it.
Six, five, four, five, five, at schools.
Five, six.
Five, six, five,
Five, six,
One, support.
Two,
One,
0,
High burn.
Thank you.
So, Agers are far between...
I thought I was saved.
ах,.
Effects tasteful, "
It's good, isn't it?
Lastly.
Come quickly to the priority,
Oh.
At work,
This is it,
What is this?
Anxiety.
I fell.
Train! Train!
It's like this, isn't it?
It really is.
You're a toy guardian.
It's so cute.
It's shaking.
Is this the last round?
I think we're going to do a second round.
I think we're gonna do a second round.
You don't want a drink?
No, thanks.
We're not going to do it, are we?
I want a picture of you and I going home.
One, two, three.
We're on the merry-go-round!
We're on the merry-go-round.
I'm in front of you
We're just the two of us.
We are two.
And Am-U is in the back.
Amou is in the back.
Hey, Romeo.
Why are you Romeo?
I'm looking at it from your boyfriend's point of view.
That's so good. Boyfriend angle.
That's what you do.
Oh, my God.
I want to see it. I want to see it.
I definitely want to see it.
It's moving.
It moved, didn't it?
Here's the view.
It's a long, long way to the related cars.
Let's have a lot of fun.
Sure thing.
Let's all run and play.
Definitely.
I'm at the end of the line.
Endgame.
It's 19:41.
You've had a lot of rides.
I'm here for your ride.
I have a favor to ask of you, sir.
We have a lot of riders.
And please don't lean against the doors.
I'd like to try one of these.
With a parachute or something.
I want to go skydiving.
I don't want to go skydiving.
You don't want to skydive?
No, I don't want to.
No, no, no, no, no.
I want someone behind me.
Like a specialist.
Follow me like this.
I'm at the top.
There... there... there is the top.
We're at the top.
We're done.
I'll show you the view.
I'll show them.
Chillo Chillo Lee.
In various fields
It's really beautiful.
Chilotillo Lee.
I had a good time today.
It was fun.
And the night view is beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
Great!
The MVP of the day was
Completed
Nippon Maru, etc.
Yokohama Minato Mirai 21
It was Yecch!
Why...
Why?
Yechi was screaming from the beginning to the end
I was screaming from the beginning to the end.
But not in a scary way.
It's just that what I was yelling was...
I mean, it's just...
Well, you're right.
I think it's more fun to scream
I think it's more fun to scream.
I'm not scared at all.
No, really.
It's fun.
We were all laughing so hard.
We were laughing so hard.
I'm exhausted today.
Exhausted.
It was fun.
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow
Tomorrow.
The lead song of the album
Wheat in the barley
Yes, sir.
That's why I'm here today.
To myself.
Take the edge off.
Yes, sir.
That's right.
Get ready for tomorrow.
Yes.
Today...
I started with Chinese food.
I ate a small basket of dumplings...
But after that...
I walked everyone to Koshoma World.
I made everyone walk to Koshoma World.
About 30 minutes.
And they're all...
Come on, let's go.
I had a look on my face like, "Hurry up!
But I got them all to come with me.
When we got here...
Come on, come on, come on.
If you come this far
From the fall of the Meiji period
In the early days of the Great Wednesday.
You ate it for the first time, didn't you?
That's right.
I also went to the Daiki-shiki.
Yes, we did.
It's a commercial facility.
A lot of new ones.
I went to...
What's that?
Now we're all going.
Oh, my God.
I want to go to a park like this.
I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go.
I want to go.
I'll come.
Yes, I'm coming.
They're here.
He's here.
Thank you very much.
We haven't had luxury since the port opened in 1859.
I'm good, man. I'm ready to show my stiff-assed face off now.
Okay, bye.
Bye-bye.
It was my day off.